<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="barnyard_animals">
        <item>Chicken</item>
        <item>Cow</item>
        <item>Horse</item>
        <item>Pig</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="lullaby_lengths">
        <item>5 min</item>
        <item>8 min</item>
        <item>10 min</item>
        <item>12 min</item>
        <item>15 min</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="months">
        <item>January</item>
        <item>February</item>
        <item>March</item>
        <item>April</item>
        <item>May</item>
        <item>June</item>
        <item>July</item>
        <item>August</item>
        <item>September</item>
        <item>October</item>
        <item>November</item>
        <item>December</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="story_sassy_cassie_page_text">
        <item></item>
        <item>Cassie’s toy box was overflowing with toys . . . little ones, big ones, cuddly ones, bouncy ones, walking ones, even talking ones.</item>
        <item>But Cassie’s favorite toys came from Mommy’s toy box with the big mirror. “I’ll need this, this, this and oh especially this!”</item>
        <item>In a flash she headed back to her room.</item>
        <item>She spread on frosty blue eye shadow. She swept on petal pink blush. She dabbed on berry delicious lipstick.</item>
        <item>“Now I look like a real princess,” Cassie said in the mirror before dashing outside.</item>
        <item>“Look, look, look at me. I’m a princess,” she sang to her big brother.</item>
        <item>“Shhhhhhh,” Dominic said, “You and Miss Kitty will scare the birds away.” He didn’t even notice Cassie’s pretty princess make-up. Maybe Mommy and Daddy will notice.</item>
        <item>“Look, look, look at me. I’m a princess,” Cassie twirled in front of Daddy’s camera. “Take a picture Daddy.”</item>
        <item>(click click click)</item>
        <item>“Look, look, look at me. I’m a princess,” Cassie swirled in front of Mommy’s easel. “Paint me, Mommy.” “Cassie you are a darling princess, but I’ve told you before, you may not wear my make-up,” Mommy said.</item>
        <item>“But I’m a princess and all real princesses wear make-up. I will wear your make-up!” “No need to get sassy, Cassie,” Mommy said, “You do not need make-up to be a princess.” “I won’t wear your make-up anymore,” Cassie promised.</item>
        <item>The next day Cassie’s friends came over to play dress-up. “I want to be a ballerina. Lily said. “Ballerinas shine when they dance on stage,” Cassie said as she brushed her friend’s face with pretty pink shimmer make-up.</item>
        <item>Lily twirled, “Now I’m ready for the spotlight.” Gigi said, “I want to be a fairy.”</item>
        <item>“Real fairies are covered in sparkly fairy dust,” Cassie said as she made her friend’s face sparkle with glittery green eye shadow.</item>
        <item>Gigi looked in the mirror and flapped her arms like wings, “Now I can flutter and fly in the sky.”</item>
        <item>Polly said, “Let’s have a tea party.”</item>
        <item>“Tea is for proper ladies and proper ladies wear fancy make-up,” Cassie said as she made-up her friend’s face with fancy colors.</item>
        <item>Polly curtsied, “It’s time for tea. One lump or two?” The shimmery ballerina, sparkly fairy and fancy lady paraded with Cassie.</item>
        <item>They frolicked and danced through the entire house until . . .</item>
        <item>“Cassie!” Mommy said sternly, “What did I say about my make-up?” “But I’m not wearing your make-up,” Cassie said, “A ballerina, a fairy, and a lady are.”</item>
        <item>“There’s make-up all over your dress. No more playing with my make-up, you have made a royal mess,” Mommy said. “I won’t play with your make-up anymore,” Cassie promised.</item>
        <item>Later that night Mommy tucked Cassie in to bed. “Mommy, only a real princess can make a royal mess, right?” Cassie asked.</item>
        <item>“That’s right, and no matter what you do you will always be my little princess. Good night,” Mommy whispered. “Good night, Queen Mommy,” Cassie said as she drifted off to dreamland.</item>
        <item>The following morning Cassie awoke bright and early. She had dreamed of all the great things princesses do and wasted no time hopping out of bed.</item>
        <item>Everyone in the kingdom was still asleep while Cassie was busy creating something special.</item>
        <item>Just as she added the final touches the door opened.</item>
        <item>“Look Mommy look, I made this just for you!” But Mommy just stood there. She did not say a word. “Don’t you like it?” Cassie asked.</item>
        <item>Finally, Mommy took in a deep breath and said, “It is beautiful, you are a true princess, but . . .” “What is it Mommy?” Cassie asked.</item>
        <item>“No more playing with the Queen’s paints!” “I won’t play with your paints anymore” Cassie promised.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="story_worst_parents_page_text">
        <item></item>
        <item>In a small town on a nice street lived a family who loved each other very much: Mom, Dad, their boys, Hank and Jack, and their pet gerbil, Gerry.</item>
        <item>Hank and Jack loved to have fun. And, one very sunny Saturday, they woke up and decided that this would be the most super fun day. So, they made up a new game, The Bouncing Tornado!</item>
        <item>But when Mom saw their room, she stopped them from jumping. “Please get dressed.” She said.</item>
        <item>They didn’t want their fun to end, so Hank and Jack made up an even more fun game at the breakfast table.</item>
        <item>But when Dad saw the mess, he wasn’t happy. “Clean up.” He said.</item>
        <item>In the afternoon, Hank and Jack created the biggest racetrack in the world.</item>
        <item>But when Mom came in, she yelled, “Game over!”</item>
        <item>At bath time, Hank and Jack had the most fun they had all day. They built their very own sailboat to sail around the world.</item>
        <item>But when Mom and Dad saw the big mess, they were really angry. “Get to bed!” They shouted.</item>
        <item>Mom and Dad did not like all the fun Hank and Jack were having. They took away all their toys as punishment. Jack and Hank were angry. “You’re the worst parents ever!” They shouted.</item>
        <item>After Mom and Dad turned off the light, Jack turned to Hank and said, “I wish we were the parents.” “Yeah,” whispered Hank, “we would have so much more fun.” Then, they drifted off to sleep.</item>
        <item>The next morning, Hank and Jack woke up and everything was different. They were big! Hank and Jack were scared, so they called for their parents. “Mom!” Hank shouted. “Dad!” Jack yelled.</item>
        <item>They came running in. But, Mom and Dad were different, too. They were little!</item>
        <item>“I guess we’re the parents now.” Hank said. “What should we do today?” Jack asked. Hank wasn’t sure. So, they decided to do what they do best.</item>
        <item>Have fun!</item>
        <item>Whoops!</item>
        <item>Since they couldn’t jump on their beds anymore, they decided to go downstairs for breakfast. And since Hank and Jack were the parents, they decided no one needed to clean up.</item>
        <item>They had lots of fun all day long!</item>
        <item>After playing all day, they were really hungry, but there was nothing to eat.</item>
        <item>And their dirty clothes made them uncomfortable, but there was nothing clean to wear.</item>
        <item>And they were really tired, but there was nowhere to sleep.</item>
        <item>Little Mom and Dad started to cry. “Don’t be sad” Jack said. “Wash your faces and brush your teeth.” Hank told them, “and we’ll clean up.”</item>
        <item>After Hank and Jack were finished cleaning, they headed upstairs to put Little Mom and Dad to bed. But when they opened the bathroom door, they couldn’t believe their eyes.</item>
        <item>Hank and Jack raced into the bathroom before the sink overflowed. Whoops! No one was having any fun. “We’re sorry we said you were the worst parents ever!” said Jack.</item>
        <item>“We want our Mom and Dad back!” cried Hank. Wet, tired, and hungry, Hank and Jack sobbed themselves to sleep.</item>
        <item>The next morning, Hank and Jack woke up and discovered that they were little again! “I think I smell pancakes!” Hank exclaimed. Hank and Jack got dressed in a hurry. But this time, they hung up their pajamas.</item>
        <item>Hank and Jack came downstairs and saw that Mom and Dad were big again!</item>
        <item>Today, Hank and Jack didn’t make a mess with their food, and they even offered to help clean up after the meal. Dad was surprised and happy. “Let’s make cleaning up fun!” Dad said.</item>
        <item>Hank and Jack helped Mom fold the laundry. And when they were done, Mom made up a new game. Laundry Basket Car!</item>
        <item>While in their bath, Hank and Jack managed to keep the bathroom neat and tidy, but they still had fun.</item>
        <item>Because Mom and Dad didn’t have lots of messes to clean up, they had time to play a game before bed.</item>
        <item>Whoops!</item>
        <item>As Mom and Dad tucked them in, Hank and Jack said, “You’re the best parents ever!” They each gave them a big hug and kiss good night.</item>
        <item>And, as they turned out the light, Mom and Dad whispered back to Hank and Jack, “We had a lot of fun with you guys today.”</item>
        <item>The End.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="toy_volumes">
        <item>Low</item>
        <item>Medium</item>
        <item>High</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="story_starburst_rainbow_journey_page_text" />
</resources>
